Look.
You'll never hit anything.
Look, look, look.
Look at the ball.
That's good.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Mei Higashimura.
I'm Kumi Sasaki.
I'm here today.
Do you know where it is?
There's a net here.
Where do you think?
Actually, I'm here at the batting center.
I'm so happy! I'm so happy! I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
I'm so glad we're at the batting cage together, even though we're privateers!
I'm so glad!
By the way, what is your usual weight?
I always weigh 90 kilos.
Me too.
Is it okay if I aim to hit it?
Yes, sir.
Ready, go!
Cue!
What's this? It's my first one.
What's this? Cue!
I'd like to put it here somewhere.
Your father is my father.
He's on it.
Okay.
Mei Muramei.
I could concentrate if you were next to me.
Helmet on. Helmet on.
Wow.
That's a great helmet.
It's a little floaty, though.
What? My hair.
Like this? Oh, it looks good.
Okay, good.
Let's get you ready for your exercises.
Check out the miken exercises.
Not quite. Maiken's a pitcher.
Maybe it's a little different.
What?
Feeling good?
How many pounds do you want to go? 90? At first, it's just a warm-up.
Here we go! Here we go! I set it at 90.
How's it going? Huh?
What? Where?
Oh, no! It's hot! Look at the ball!
- What? It's coming, right? - It's coming. You know, just in case the video...
- Wait, no, no, no, no, no! - It's okay, it's okay. We're still warming up.
It's still warming up, but the sun's too bright.
It's still there. It's still coming.
- It's coming!
Wait, it falls down every time!
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's hot!
It's hot.
This could be bad.
It's okay, it's okay. Calm down.
Watch the ball.Watch the ball.
Pull it.
Oh, wait a minute, that's pretty good.
Oh!
Wow.
Beware of the pearl ball.
Nice.
Pearl.
I'm getting better and better.
Don't worry, it's just the beginning.
I'm just going with the flow.
That's good. That's good.
The ball's hurting really bad.
It's gone down here.
Is the camera out of hot water or something?
Oh, no!
The ball May hit.
That's a big one!
Yes, it is!
It's hot!
Wait a minute.
Now that was a good hit, wasn't it?
Not bad.
Watch the ball.
Watch the ball. No.
Is it done?
Looks like it's over.
It's over!
It's over.
Oh, my God, this is so bad.
I really couldn't do it at all.
You couldn't do it?
But you got it right.
Let's just use the parts that were right.
This was pretty bad.
No, not really.
It's the first time.
This one...
That one.
Here you go.
Helmets on.
Yes, sir.
How many kilometers?
Uh, 90 kilometers.
Okay.
A little bit.
I'm counting on you.
Cool!
Maybe a little short on the bat.
I think this one's better.
Is this one heavier?
Okay, here we go.
Let the games begin!
Let's go!
Go!
Watch the ball!
I'm turning into a weird character.
Oh, he waved at me!Oh, he waved at me!
Yay!
Hihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihi!
Hee-hee-hee-hee
One turn
Hee-hee-hee!
I can do it!
It's not hitting at all!
It won't hit at all!
You're gonna win!
You'll win!
Ha-ha-ha!
What's the matter? Isn't it hard today?
It's so hard today!
Look at the ball!
Look!
Look, look, look, look, look!
I can't hit it!
Watch the ball! Look at the ball!
I think it's a little low. I don't know why.
All right.
I'm going for a home run!
I'm fired up.
Home run, home run!
Home run!
Go for it!
It's hot!
It's extremely hot today!
Oh, by the way, it looks good!
Great!
I want to hit a homura!
Homura, go!
Oh, no.
You gotta pull it more.
You gotta pull, you gotta pull the ball.
Uh-huh.
Ha-ha-ha.
You're pathetic.
Wait, wait, is there more? Is there more?
There's more. There's more.
Did I just sing something?
I'm pathetic.
Ha-ha-ha.
Can we get closer?
Is it over?
Oh, hey, it's over.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm not happy with the results.
But it's fun.
I'd like to be able to hit more.
Hey, I can hit more, for sure
Go for it!
I'm going to put my mind to it!
Please do.
Wait, I'm embarrassed. I don't want to do this.
I'll put my mind to it.
I'll get into it.Please.
I'm so embarrassed I'm so embarrassed I struck out so much
It's so cute!
I'm so embarrassed. It's so cute.
But seriously...
Oh, wow.
Sounds good.
Declaration of a home run
Heh heh heh
wow!
Wow.
He's timing it right.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's okay.
I got it.
It's coming together.
It's a good hit.
I'd like to hit the red circle.
Please. Home run.
Wow.
Almost a home run.
That's great.
Thank you for watching.
It's one with the ground.
I can do it.
Oh, my God, I fell.
Good job, guys.
Thank you very much.
You're very polite.
What's wrong?
Just one.
It flew off the roof.
It was amazing.
But it hit harder than the other one, that's for sure.
It was kind of close.
It was so close.
I couldn't hit the whole circle.
I'm going to go now.
Please do.
I'll do it.
It's kind of low. It's low.
This is...
Oh! Should I get closer?
Oh!
Wait, maybe the bat is too short.
Let's try to get it out of this hole.
Let's hit it.
Oh, that's good.
Beware of the curl ball!
Zoom, zoom, zoom.
Cool!
Go!
Maybe I'll raise it higher.
Nice.
I'm a tough opponent.Strong Enemy.
Strong Enemy Appears
Today's Au
Today's woo
Today's aw...
Yeah!
Yay!
Oops.
It's over.
That was fun.
It was a lot of fun.
At first, I thought... I thought it might not go well.
I thought it might not work at first, but then it got better and better.
We could have a showdown.
I couldn't do it this time.
I'd like to do it again.
Please subscribe to my channel and give me a high rating!
Bye bye!